Companies should focus on building sustainable businesses, improving profitability and
creating long-term value rather than merely chasing higher share prices,
NSE MD and CEO Ashish Chauhan said on Friday.
Addressing the 9th JITO Incubation & Innovation Foundation (JIIF) Day
event, he said a company's market valuation should be a
reflection of its business performance and growth.
The objective of an entrepreneur should be to expand the
business and increase shareholder value through stronger fundamentals, he suggested.
"If the company's profit increases, the share value should increase.
You cannot keep increasing value without creating actual business growth,"
Chauhan said.